John A. Holmes Papers MS007
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Scrapbooks, 1929 -- 1961; MS007.009; 10.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of bound scrapbooks compiled by Holmes between 1928 and 1961. Between 1938 and 1956 Holmes appears to have kept the scrapbooks only sporadically, and there are only three books which span this period. The books contain clippings of poems, articles, pictures, book reviews and other materials about poets and poetry, collected by Holmes. The early scrapbooks emphasize the relationship between poems and pictures, and feature numerous pairings of poems by Holmes with pictures that illustrate or inspired the verses. Holmes used the scrapbooks for research and reference featuring poets whose work he prized, and as a way of mediating his relationship with the world of poetry. As Holmes began to make a name for himself as a poet, an increasing proportion of the contents of the scrapbooks has to do with his own career, including clippings of some of his published poems, articles and book reviews about Holmes and his books, and acceptance and rejection letters. For each scrapbook, the existence of unusual or important items beyond the scope of those included above is indicated in the item record.
  Additional material was added to the Holmes collection in June 2009 by Laura Cutter. Two scrapbooks were added to this series. The first scrapbook was made by John Holmes for the Saturday Review's contest for the best poems published in the Saturday Review between May 1956 and May 1957. The second scrapbook is a mimeographed copy of all of the Saturday Review contest poems.
  This series is arranged in numerical order as established by Holmes. Arrangement generally corresponds to chronological order.
  - Scrapbook, 1902 -- 1929; MS007.009.023.00001; Holmes, John (Box 23)
    Volume titled "Poems with pictures".
    Volume
    1
  - Scrapbook, 1929; MS007.009.024.00001; Holmes, John (Box 24)
    Volume titled "Poems with pictures"; clippings of Holmes' poems written as DONJON in the Boston Herald on p. 63-8. Some acceptance/rejection letters. Poems paired with sketches by Holmes.
    2
  - Scrapbook, 1904 -- 1929; MS007.009.025.00001; Holmes, John (Box 25)
    3
  - Scrapbook, 1906 -- 1929; MS007.009.026.00001; Holmes, John (Box 26)
    4
  - Scrapbook, 1910 -- 1929; MS007.009.027.00001; Holmes, John (Box 27)
    Includes index to sources of clippings on inside of back cover.
    5
  - Scrapbook, 1901 -- 1930; MS007.009.028.00001; Holmes, John (Box 28)
    Handwritten poem by Robert Hillyer on p. 34.
    6
  - Scrapbook, 1930; MS007.009.029.00001; Holmes, John (Box 29)
    7
  - Scrapbook, 1931; MS007.009.030.00001; Holmes, John (Box 30)
    8
  - Scrapbook, 1908 -- 1931; MS007.009.031.00001; Holmes, John (Box 31)
    9
  - Scrapbook, 1931-12 -- 1932-07; MS007.009.032.0001; Holmes, John (Box 32)
    Prefaced with short poem "About scrapbooks". Several poems, some handwritten, from Theodore Rothke, p. 37-52.
    10
  - Scrapbook, 1932; MS007.009.033.00001; Holmes, John (Box 33)
    11
  - Scrapbook, 1932-12 -- 1933; MS007.009.034.00001; Holmes, John (Box 34)
    12
  - Scrapbook, 1933; MS007.009.035.00001; Holmes, John (Box 35)
    Letters from Stanley Kunitz p. 116, and Louis Untermeyer p. 14; handwritten poem by Christopher Morley, p. 140.
    13
  - Scrapbook, 1933 -- 1934; MS007.009.036.00001; Holmes, John (Box 36)
    Letter from Archibald MacLeish, p. 68.
    14
  - Scrapbook, 1934; MS007.009.037.00001; Holmes, John (Box 37)
    15
  - Scrapbook, 1934 -- 1935; MS007.009.038.00001; Holmes, John (Box 38)
    Several pages of autographs clipped from letters, including Robert Hillyer, Mark Van Doren, Archibald MacLeish, Gilbert Maxwell, Wilbert Snow, John Crowe Ransom, Harold Vinal, Ralph Humphries, James Rorty, Merill Moore, Stanley Kunitz, Bernart DeVoto, Christopher Morley; Christmas card from Merrill Moore
    16
  - Scrapbook, 1935; MS007.009.039.00001; Holmes, John (Box 39)
    17
  - Scrapbook, 1935; MS007.009.040.00001; Holmes, John (Box 40)
    Handwritten poem by Theodore Roethke, p. 50-1.
    18
  - Scrapbook, 1935 -- 1936; MS007.009.041.00001; Holmes, John (Box 41)
    19
  - Scrapbook, 1936; MS007.009.042.00001; Holmes, John (Box 42)
    Handwritten poem by Theodore Roethke, p. 28; envelope addressed to Holmes by Robert Frost, p. 98
    20
  - Scrapbook, 1936 -- 1937; MS007.009.043.00001; Holmes, John (Box 43)
    Christmas cards from other poets including David McCord, p. 75.
    21
  - Scrapbook, 1937; MS007.009.044.00001; Holmes, John (Box 44)
    Annotated poem from C. F. McIntyre, p. 56-7
    22
  - Scrapbook, 1938; MS007.009.045.00001; Holmes, John (Box 45)
    23
  - Scrapbook, 1938 -- 1953; MS007.009.046.00001; Holmes, John (Box 46)
    Letters from Archibald MacLeish, p. 12-3.
    24
  - Scrapbook, 1942 -- 1953; MS007.009.047.00001; Holmes, John (Box 47)
    Poem by Jeremy Ingalls inscribed to Holmes, p. 8-9; letters from Carl Sandburg p. 32-3; notes explaining the context of each of the items in the scrapbook, p. 139-44.
    25
  - War Posters Scrapbook, 1944; MS007.009.047.00002; Holmes, John (Box 47)
    Holmes' catalogue of World War II posters, organized by "genre" or poster production series. Also includes images of posters clipped from periodicals, some hand-colored, as well as Holmes' own drawings of posters.
  - Scrapbook, 1953 -- 1956; MS007.009.048.00001; Holmes, John (Box 48)
    Includes clippings of advertisements with literary references.
    26
  - Scrapbook, 1956 -- 1957; MS007.009.049.00001; Holmes, John (Box 49)
    27
  - Scrapbook, 1957 -- 1958; MS007.009.050.00001; Holmes, John (Box 50)
    28
  - Scrapbook, 1958; MS007.009.051.00001; Holmes, John (Box 51)
    Note from Louise Brogan p. 127.
    29
  - Scrapbook, 1958; MS007.009.052.00001; Holmes, John (Box 52)
    30
  - Scrapbook, 1959; MS007.009.052.00002; Holmes, John (Box 52)
    Letter from David McCord, p. 81.
    31
  - Scrapbook, 1959; MS007.009.053.00001; Holmes, John (Box 53)
    Letter from Stanley Kunitz, p. 12
    32
  - Scrapbook, 1959 -- 1960; MS007.009.054.00001; Holmes, John (Box data_value_missing_8a0215777737a2d99fdf55396aecd39d)
    Robert Lowell letter, p. 112.
    33
  - Scrapbook, 1960; MS007.009.055.00001; Holmes, John (Box data_value_missing_8a0215777737a2d99fdf55396aecd39d)
    34
  - Scrapbook, 1960; MS007.009.056.00001; Holmes, John (Box 56)
    Letters from Win Scott, p. 52, and Witter Brynner, p. 53.
    35
  - Scrapbook, 1961; MS007.009.057.00001; Holmes, John (Box 57)
    36
  - Scrapbook, 1961; MS007.009.058.00001; Holmes, John (Box 58)
    37
  - The Black Book One, 1950; MS007.009.059.00001; Holmes, John (Box MS007 Shared 4)
  - The Black Book Two, 1950 -- 1951; MS007.009.059.00002; Holmes, John (Box MS007 Shared 4)
  - Saturday Review Prize scrapbook, 1956 -- 1957; MS007.009.071.00001 (Box 71)
    Added to collection in June 2009. John Holmes made this scrapbook for the Saturday Review's contest for the best poems published in the Saturday Review between May 1956 and May 1957. Holmes served as one of the three judges for the contest.
  - Saturday Review Prize scrapbook [mimeograph], 1956 -- 1957; MS007.009.071.00002 (Box 71)
    Added to collection in June 2009. This is a mimeograph of all of the poems contained in John Holmes' scrapbook for the Saturday Review's contest from 1956-1957. All the poems were retyped in this volume, presumably for ease of selection. Holmes served as one of the three judges for the contest.
- Photographs, 1880 -- 1980; 1950 -- 1961; MS007.010; 0.5 Linear Feet; 127 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of photographs of Holmes and other poets, family, and friends. The bulk of the material dates from 1950 to 1961. Many of the photographs are formal and informal portraits of Holmes, and publicity photos of Holmes and poets who visited Tufts. The early photos are of Holmes' parents and family.
  These loose prints have been stored separately from the collection. See the barcode in the location field for the location of the print.
  This series is arranged as found.
  - John Holmes in front of Starkweather Gate in winter, February 15, 1935; MS007.010.DO.00120; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    Gates; People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - Early photo of John Holmes 1904-1962 (John Albert Holmes, Jr.), 1907; MS007.010.DO.00144; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1935; MS007.010.DO.00145; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1931; MS007.010.DO.00146; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, March 13, 1935; MS007.010.DO.00147; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; Portraits; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John; Dept. of English
  - John Holmes, 1948; MS007.010.DO.00148; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, May 13, 1935; MS007.010.DO.00149; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Portraits; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John; Dept. of English
  - John Holmes, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00150; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    People; Portraits; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00151; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Faculty; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00152; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    Faculty; People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, March 13, 1935; MS007.010.DO.00153; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Portraits; Faculty; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00154; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    People; Faculty; Portraits; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1930; MS007.010.DO.00155; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; Portraits; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00156; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, January 6, 1946; MS007.010.DO.00157; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00158; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00159; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00160; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00161; Rossiter, Peter (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00162; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, November, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00163; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes teaching, October, 1957; MS007.010.DO.00164; Unknown (Box Shared 51)
    People; Faculty; Students; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, November, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00165; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00166; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00167; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, November, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00168; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, July, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00169; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00170; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, c., 1960; MS007.010.DO.00171; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
    John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, Summer, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00172; Perkis, Philip (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, October 27, 1961; MS007.010.DO.00173; Perkis, Philip (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00178; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, August 31, 1937; MS007.010.DO.00179; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, August 31, 1937; MS007.010.DO.00180; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    photographic print; Holmes, John
  - Mark Van Doren, Morris Bishop, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00181; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes, Writers Workshop, 7-28-54, 1954; MS007.010.DO.00182; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes (with students), 1960; MS007.010.DO.00183; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Sheldon Glueck with winners of college writing contest, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00184; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes with New England Poetry Club, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00185; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_c33db48e96fb96303b0f6b3b314c8c2e)
  - John Holmes with students, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00186 (Box Shared 26)
    Students; Faculty; John A. Holmes, papers; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00187; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, Dr. and Mrs Glueck, winners of poetry contest, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00188; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, Robert Frost, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00189; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, Robert Frost, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00190; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes and Robert Frost, 1958; MS007.010.DO.00191; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
    John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John; Tufts College; Tufts University
  - John Holmes with Maxine Kumin, Harold Melvin, and Anne Sexton, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00192; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
    John A. Holmes, papers; Poets; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes, (1958), MS007.010.DO.00193; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, New England Poetry Club, c., 1960; MS007.010.DO.00194; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00195; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes and John C. Ransom, 1958; MS007.010.DO.00196; Duette Photographers (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
    Poets; photographic print; Holmes, John; Ransom, John C.
  - John Holmes, John C. Ransom, [1950's], MS007.010.DO.00197; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, John C. Ransom, [1950's], MS007.010.DO.00198; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, late 1950s, 1958; MS007.010.DO.00199; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, Robert Frost, [1950's], MS007.010.DO.00200; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, John Ciardi [1950's], MS007.010.DO.00201; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, John Ciardi [1950's], MS007.010.DO.00202; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, John Ciardi, 1959; MS007.010.DO.00203; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - John Holmes, 1958; MS007.010.DO.00204; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - Robert Frost and John Holmes, Nov., 1951; MS007.010.DO.00205; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John; Frost, Robert
  - John Holmes, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00206; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Homes, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00207; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, July, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00208; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Summer Writer's Workshop, U. New Hampshire, mid 1950's, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00209; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_2e267237c7da7c1c9673ba729be714db)
  - Open Letter To Postmen, Illustrations for Fair Warning, 1939; MS007.010.DO.00210; Kane, Henry B. (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
    John A. Holmes, papers; Holmes, John; Tufts College; Tufts University
  - Pains of Poetry, Illustration for Fair Warning, 1939; MS007.010.DO.00211; Kane, Henry B. (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Fair Warning, Illustration for Fair Warning, 1939; MS007.010.DO.00212; Kane, Henry B. (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Calling All Cartoonists, Illustrations for Fair Warning, 1939; MS007.010.DO.00213; Kane, Henry B. (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Portrait of John Holmes, 2-21-63, 1963; MS007.010.DO.00214; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes Memorial, Tufts Campus [1965}, MS007.010.DO.00215; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
    Memorials; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John
  - John Holmes Memorial, 1965; MS007.010.DO.00216; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - The Certainty, An interpretation of John Holmes' poem [no date], MS007.010.DO.00217; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - John A. Holmes, John L. Holmes, Doris Kirk Holmes, Fall, 1948; MS007.010.DO.00218; Bachrach, Bradford (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Jolhn Holmes and family, 1915; MS007.010.DO.00219; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Dorothy Holmes Maguire, 1925; MS007.010.DO.00220; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Dorothy Holmes Maguire, 1949; MS007.010.DO.00221; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Sarah Holmes, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00222; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, Doris Holmes, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00223; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes, Doris Holmes, Evan Holmes March, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00224; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Ludlow Holmes March, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00225; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Ludlow Holmes, Evan Kirk Holmes March, 1952; MS007.010.DO.00226; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Doris Holmes, Evan Holmes, Margaret Holmes December, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00227; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - John Holmes, Doris Holmes at Brandeis University Summer, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00228; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Becca Lithgow, January, 1951; MS007.010.DO.00229; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
    People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print
  - John Albert Holmes, Sr., ca.1910, MS007.010.DO.00230; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Mary Holmes, 1890; MS007.010.DO.00231; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Mary Holmes, 1880; MS007.010.DO.00232; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Albert Holmes Sr., 1940; MS007.010.DO.00233; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - John Albert Holmes, Sr., 1910; MS007.010.DO.00234; Unknown (Box Shared 51)
  - John Holmes' Vermont House, 9-22-46, 1946; MS007.010.DO.00235; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes House, 28 Billingham St., 1945; MS007.010.DO.00236; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Holmes' house, 28 Billingham St., 1945; MS007.010.DO.00237; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Philip Booth, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00238; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
    People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Booth, Philip
  - John Ciardi, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00239; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Ciardi, John Anthony
  - Richard Wilbur, 1959; MS007.010.DO.00240; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Wilbur, Richard
  - John Ciardi, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00241; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Ciardi, John Anthony
  - John Ciardi, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00242; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Basil Davenport, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00243; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Richard Eberhart, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00244; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Jeremy Ingalls, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00245; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Jeremy Ingalls, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00246; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Maxine Kumin, 1960 January 13; MS007.010.DO.00247; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Kumin, Maxine
  - Tom Burns Haber, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00248; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Donald Hall, August, 1956; MS007.010.DO.00249; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - A.E. Housman, 1926; MS007.010.DO.00250; Dodd, Francis (Box Shared 26)
  - Dilys Laing, 1950; MS007.010.DO.00251; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Archibald Macleish, 1958 October 14; MS007.010.DO.00252; Unknown (Box Shared 117)
    John A. Holmes, papers; copy negative; copy negative; MacLeish, Archibald; Tufts College; Tufts University
  - Phyllis McGinley, 1910 -- 1934; MS007.010.DO.00253; Underwood and Underwood (Box Shared 26)
    Caption reads: Please credit Underwood and Underwood. Phyllis McGinley whose verses are well known to readers of the New Yorker, will have a collection of verses, On The Contrary, on the October 24th list of Doubelday Doran.
    Poets; photographic print; McGinley, Phyllis
  - Sam Morse, 1956; MS007.010.DO.00254; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - John Crowe Ransom, 1935; MS007.010.DO.00255; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - John Crowe Ransom, 1959; MS007.010.DO.00256; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Edwin Arlington Robinson, 1916; MS007.010.DO.00257; Perry, Lilla Cabot (Box Shared 26)
  - Carl Sandberg, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00258 (Box Shared 117)
    John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Sandburg, Carl; Tufts College; Tufts University
  - Carl Sandberg, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00259; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - May Sarton, 1945; MS007.010.DO.00260; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Richard Wilbur, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00261; Unknown (Box Shared 117)
    John A. Holmes, papers; copy negative; copy negative; Wilbur, Richard; Tufts College; Tufts University
  - Frances Randall, 1939; MS007.010.DO.00262; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Frances Randall, 9-13-59, 1959; MS007.010.DO.00263; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Frances Ames Randall, 1888; MS007.010.DO.00264; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Frances Randall, 1956; MS007.010.DO.00265; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Frances Randall, 1944; MS007.010.DO.00266; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Sommerset Dam, 1912; MS007.010.DO.00267; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_56af109cb9ad8fd990acb66f9e18b849)
  - Charles J. Connick, 1940; MS007.010.DO.00268; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
  - Portrait of John Holmes, March, 1960; MS007.010.DO.00269; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    People; John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John; Tufts College; Tufts University; Dept. of English
  - Portrait of John Holmes by Myron J. Files, 1955; MS007.010.DO.00270; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_017f0f6b806efe92050eb4f65866283e)
    John A. Holmes, papers; photographic print; Holmes, John; Files, Professor Myron J.; Tufts College; Tufts University
  - Portrait of John Holmes, 1980; MS007.010.DO.00271; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_017f0f6b806efe92050eb4f65866283e)